The company wants me to sign an endorsement deal with Qingmu.
تريد الشركة مني التوقيع على اتفاقية تأييد مع Qingmu.
Qingmu is just a second-rate, small company.
إن شركة Qingmu هي مجرد شركة صغيرة من الدرجة الثانية.
What right do they have to work with me?
ما هو الحق الذي لديهم للعمل معي؟
President Zhang, is this about the endorsement fee?
السيد الرئيس تشانغ، هل يتعلق الأمر برسوم التأييد؟
No matter how much they offer,
بغض النظر عن مقدار ما يقدمونه،
I won't sign it.
لن أوقع عليه.
What endorsement fee?
ما هي رسوم التأييد؟
It's your honor to work with Qingmu.
إنه شرف لك أن تعمل مع Qingmu.
It's also an honor for our Miracle Media.
إنه شرف أيضًا لمؤسستنا Miracle Media.
We'll sign this contract right away.
سوف نوقع هذا العقد على الفور.
As for the endorsement fee,
أما بالنسبة لرسوم التصديق،
we don't want a single cent.
نحن لا نريد سنتا واحدا.
It must be free.
يجب أن يكون مجانيًا.
Free? President Zhang, are you crazy?
حر؟ الرئيس تشانغ، هل أنت مجنون؟
I don't agree.
انا لا اوافق.
This will affect my reputation as Best Actress.
هذا سوف يؤثر على سمعتي كأفضل ممثلة.
Shut up.
اسكت.
This is the company's decision.
هذا قرار الشركة.
It's not your place to comment.
ليس من مكانك التعليق.
Let me remind you,
دعني أذكرك،
you're a popular star because the company made you one.
أنت نجم مشهور لأن الشركة جعلتك كذلك.
The contract is also in the company's hands.
العقد في يد الشركة أيضًا.
Miracle Media can make you famous,
يمكن لوسائل الإعلام المعجزة أن تجعلك مشهورًا،
but we can also make you disappear overnight.
ولكن يمكننا أيضًا أن نجعلك تختفي بين عشية وضحاها.
But why is this happening?
ولكن لماذا يحدث هذا؟
I need an explanation.
أحتاج إلى توضيح.
You're not qualified to know.
أنت لست مؤهلاً للمعرفة.
All you need to know
كل ما تحتاج إلى معرفته
is that if you don't sign this contract,
هو أنه إذا لم توقع هذا العقد،
not only will the company blacklist you,
لن تقوم الشركة بإدراجك في القائمة السوداء فحسب،
but you'll have no place in the entertainment industry from now on.
ولكن لن يكون لك مكان في صناعة الترفيه من الآن فصاعدا.
Sign it now.
قم بالتوقيع الآن.
Hurry up.
اسرع.
President Su.
الرئيس سو.
Please keep this contract safe.
يرجى الحفاظ على هذا العقد في مكان آمن.
You can order Xiao Yaqi around however you like.
يمكنك أن تطلب من Xiao Yaqi كيفما تشاء.
If you have any other requests, just let us know.
إذا كان لديك أي طلبات أخرى، فقط أخبرنا بذلك.
Miracle Media will absolutely,
سوف تقوم شركة Miracle Media بالتأكيد،
fully cooperate with you unconditionally.
التعاون معك بشكل كامل ودون قيد أو شرط.
Thank you, President Zhang.
شكرا لك، الرئيس تشانغ.
So, who's the clown now?
إذن، من هو المهرج الآن؟
You.
أنت.
We didn't spend a single cent.
لم ننفق سنتا واحدا.
We actually managed to sign Xiao Yaqi.
لقد تمكنا بالفعل من التوقيع مع شياو ياتشي.
Is this just another coincidence?
هل هذه مجرد مصادفة أخرى؟
No.
لا.
I don't believe it.
انا لا اصدق ذلك.
This can't be a coincidence.
لا يمكن أن يكون هذا مجرد مصادفة.
It can't be luck either.
لا يمكن أن يكون الحظ أيضًا.
And it definitely isn't because Chu Jiangchao is just a nice guy.
وبالتأكيد ليس لأن تشو جيانجتشاو مجرد رجل لطيف.
Tell me, what's really going on?
أخبرني، ماذا يحدث حقًا؟
Do you want the truth or a lie?
هل تريد الحقيقة أم الكذب؟
Of course I want the truth.
بالطبع أريد الحقيقة.
You wouldn't believe the truth anyway.
لن تصدق الحقيقة على أية حال.
Then tell me a lie, let's hear it.
إذن أخبرني كذبة، دعنا نسمعها.
The lie is, I have a friend who's good at voice imitation.
الكذبة هي أن لدي صديقًا جيدًا في تقليد الصوت.
I asked him to imitate Chu Jiangchao's voice.
طلبت منه أن يقلد صوت تشو جيانجتشاو.
He called the boss of Miracle.
اتصل برئيس المعجزة.
And fooled him just like that.
وخدعته هكذا تمامًا.
That boss has been in business for decades.
لقد كان هذا الرئيس في العمل لعقود من الزمن.
How could he be fooled so easily by you?
كيف يمكن أن ينخدع بك بسهولة؟
If you walk by the river often,
إذا كنت تمشي بجانب النهر في كثير من الأحيان،
how can you not get your shoes wet?
كيف لا تبتل حذائك؟
It wasn't just the boss of Miracle.
لم يكن الأمر مجرد رئيس المعجزة.
Even Zhou Pengfei from Tiange Group
حتى تشو بينغفي من مجموعة تيانج
was fooled by me the same way.
لقد خدعني بنفس الطريقة.
Enough, tell the truth.
كفى، قل الحقيقة.
The truth is, Chu Jiangchao is my underling.
الحقيقة هي أن تشو جيانجتشاو هو مرؤوسيه.
I just make a call,
لقد قمت بإجراء مكالمة فقط
tell him to do something,
اطلب منه أن يفعل شيئا ما،
and he does it.
وهو يفعل ذلك.
That "truth" of yours
تلك "الحقيقة" الخاصة بك
is even less believable than the lie.
أقل تصديقًا من الكذبة.
See, I told you.
انظر، لقد أخبرتك.
You'd never believe the truth.
لن تصدق الحقيقة أبدًا.
You know,
أنت تعرف،
if you'd told me this before,
لو كنت قلت لي هذا من قبل،
I definitely would've thought you were joking.
أعتقد بالتأكيد أنك كنت تمزح.
But now...
ولكن الآن...
What's going on now?
ماذا يحدث الآن؟
Do you believe it now?
هل تصدق ذلك الآن؟
I don't know.
لا أعرف.
I just feel like I understand you less and less.
أشعر فقط أنني أفهمك بشكل أقل وأقل.
I always feel like you have a lot of secrets.
أشعر دائمًا أن لديك الكثير من الأسرار.
You're just an ordinary delivery guy.
أنت مجرد رجل توصيل عادي.
But you can do so many incredible things.
لكن بإمكانك القيام بالعديد من الأشياء المذهلة.
You're like a bottomless pit.
أنت مثل حفرة بلا قاع.
The more people want to figure you out,
كلما زاد عدد الأشخاص الذين يريدون فهمك،
the deeper they fall in.
كلما سقطوا أعمق.
There's nothing I can do.
لا يوجد شيء أستطيع فعله.
Maybe that's a man's charm.
ربما هذا هو سحر الرجل.
Honey, don't tell me
عزيزتي لا تخبريني
you've really fallen for me?
هل وقعت في حبي حقا؟
Who—who likes you?
من-من يحبك؟
We're just contract spouses.
نحن مجرد أزواج متعاقدين.
I don't have any feelings for you.
ليس لدي أي مشاعر تجاهك.
Then just now, you
ثم الآن فقط، أنت
I didn't do anything just now!
لم أفعل أي شيء الآن!
I'm tired. I'm going to sleep.
أنا متعب. سأذهب للنوم.
You're going to sleep again?
هل ستنام مرة أخرى؟
Don't overthink it. You're just contract spouses.
لا تفكروا كثيرًا، أنتم مجرد زوجين مرتبطين بعقد.
Right.
يمين.
Contract spouses.
أزواج العقد.
Just a second-tier celebrity,
مجرد شخصية مشهورة من الدرجة الثانية،
actually caught Mr. Gao's attention.
لقد لفت انتباه السيد جاو بالفعل.
He even specifically asked her to be the spokesperson.
بل وطلب منها بشكل خاص أن تكون المتحدثة باسمه.
Could it be
هل يمكن أن يكون
that Mr. Gao is interested in her?
أن السيد جاو مهتم بها؟
Have Director Zhang Yimu start preparing an international blockbuster immediately.
اطلب من المخرج تشانغ ييمو أن يبدأ في تحضير فيلم عالمي ضخم على الفور.
Xiao Yaqi must play the female lead.
يجب على شياو ياتشي أن تلعب دور البطولة النسائية.
I want, in the shortest time possible,
أريد في أقصر وقت ممكن،
to make her an international superstar.
لتجعلها نجمة عالمية.
Also, spread the word.
وأيضاً، نشر الكلمة.
Tell those who have bad intentions toward Xiao Yaqi
أخبر أولئك الذين لديهم نوايا سيئة تجاه شياو يا تشي
to stay far away.
للبقاء بعيدا.
Anyone who dares touch a hair on her head
كل من يجرؤ على لمس شعرة من رأسها
will be going against me, Chu Jiangchao.
سوف يذهب ضدي، تشو جيانجتشاو.
They'll bear the consequences themselves.
وسوف يتحملون العواقب بأنفسهم.
Bastard.
نذل.
Why should I be a spokesperson for Su Qingyan's lousy company?
لماذا يجب أن أكون المتحدث الرسمي لشركة Su Qingyan الرديئة؟
Do I, Xiao Yaqi, not care about my reputation?
هل أنا، شياو ياتشي، لا أهتم بسمعتي؟
Well said.
أحسنت القول.
Who are you?
من أنت؟
This is a private club.
هذا نادي خاص.
Get out.
اخرج.
Miss Xiao, there's no need to be afraid.
آنسة شياو، ليس هناك حاجة للخوف.
We're all in the same boat.
نحن جميعا في نفس القارب.
Let me introduce myself.
دعني أعرفك بنفسي.
I'm Song Haoyang.
أنا سونغ هاويانغ.
I came here today specifically to discuss a collaboration with Miss Xiao.
لقد جئت إلى هنا اليوم خصيصًا لمناقشة التعاون مع الآنسة شياو.
So you're the young master of the Song family from Yun City.
إذن أنت السيد الشاب لعائلة سونغ من مدينة يون.
What did Young Master Song mean by what he just said?
ماذا يقصد السيد الشاب سونغ بما قاله للتو؟
My meaning is very simple.
معناي بسيط جداً.
Miss Xiao, don't you dislike Qingmu Group?
آنسة شياو، ألا تكرهين مجموعة Qingmu؟
That's perfect.
هذا ممتاز.
I also have a grudge against Qingmu.
لدي أيضا ضغينة ضد تشينجمو.
Why don't we join forces to teach Qingmu a lesson?
لماذا لا نجمع قوانا لتعليم تشينجمو درسًا؟
A lesson? How?
درس؟ كيف؟
I heard that.
لقد سمعت ذلك.
Qingmu Group signed an endorsement contract with you, Miss Xiao.
لقد وقعت مجموعة Qingmu عقد تأييد معك، يا آنسة شياو.
They're about to hold a press conference.
إنهم على وشك عقد مؤتمر صحفي.
As long as you publicly break the contract at the press conference,
طالما أنك تنتهك العقد علنًا في المؤتمر الصحفي،
and turn against them,
وانقلب عليهم
then with the media my Song family has arranged to spread the news,
ثم قامت عائلة سونغ بالتنسيق مع وسائل الإعلام لنشر الخبر،
I guarantee.
انا اضمن.
Qingmu Group will be utterly ruined.
مجموعة تشينغمو سوف تتعرض للتدمير الكامل.
You think I don't want to?
هل تعتقد أنني لا أريد ذلك؟
My contract is in Miracle's hands.
عقدي في يد ميراكل.
If I dare to break the contract,
إذا تجرأت على كسر العقد،
the company will immediately blacklist me.
ستقوم الشركة بإدراجي على الفور في القائمة السوداء.
Who will take responsibility for the consequences?
من سيتحمل مسؤولية العواقب؟
Will it be your Song family?
هل ستكون عائلتك سونغ؟
Miss Xiao, you're overthinking it.
آنسة شياو، أنت تفكرين في الأمر أكثر من اللازم.
My Song family can't do it,
عائلتي سونغ لا تستطيع فعل ذلك،
but someone else can.
ولكن شخص آخر يستطيع ذلك.
Who?
من؟
Chu Jiangchao, the head of Zhongyu Entertainment.
Chu Jiangchao، رئيس Zhongyu Entertainment.
President Chu.
الرئيس تشو.
He's the godfather of the entertainment industry.
إنه الأب الروحي لصناعة الترفيه.
He has abundant resources.
لديه موارد وفيرة.
He can make someone famous with ease.
بإمكانه أن يجعل شخصًا مشهورًا بسهولة.
I'm just a second-tier minor celebrity.
أنا مجرد أحد المشاهير من الدرجة الثانية.
How could I possibly be connected to such a big shot?
كيف يمكنني أن أكون متصلاً بمثل هذا الشخص الكبير؟
Maybe others can't,
ربما لا يستطيع الآخرون ذلك،
but you definitely can, Miss Xiao.
لكن بالتأكيد يمكنك ذلك، يا آنسة شياو.
What do you mean by that?
ماذا تقصد بذلك؟
Miss Xiao, you probably don't know yet.
آنسة شياو، ربما لا تعرفين ذلك بعد.
President Chu personally made a statement.
وقد أدلى الرئيس تشو ببيان شخصي.
He warned the entire entertainment industry.
وحذر صناعة الترفيه بأكملها.
No matter who it is,
بغض النظر عمن هو،
no one is allowed to lay a finger on you.
لا يُسمح لأحد بوضع إصبعه عليك.
Otherwise, they're going against Chu Jiangchao.
وإلا فإنهم سيذهبون ضد تشو جيانجتشاو.
Think carefully about what that means.
فكر جيدا فيما يعنيه هذا.
This shows that.
وهذا يدل على ذلك.
President Chu has taken a liking to you.
لقد أعجب بك الرئيس تشو.
And he considers you his forbidden treasure.
ويعتبرك كنزه المحرم.
President Chu likes me?
هل الرئيس تشو يحبني؟
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
Could there be a mistake?
هل يمكن أن يكون هناك خطأ؟
Of course it's true.
بالطبع هذا صحيح.
And I've even heard some rumors.
وقد سمعت أيضًا بعض الشائعات.
President Chu has arranged for a famous director
لقد رتب الرئيس تشو لمخرج مشهور
to create an international blockbuster tailored just for you.
لإنشاء فيلم عالمي ضخم مصمم خصيصًا لك.
As the female lead.
كالبطلة النسائية.
It has to be you.
لا بد أن تكون أنت.
There's actually such a good thing?
هل يوجد في الواقع شيء جيد كهذا؟
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
Miss Xiao, this is Zhang Yimu.
السيدة شياو، هذا هو تشانغ ييمو.
I'm about to start preparing for an international blockbuster.
أنا على وشك البدء في التحضير لفيلم دولي ضخم.
I'd like to invite you to be the leading actress.
أرغب في دعوتك لتكون الممثلة الرئيسية.
I wonder if you have time in your schedule?
أتساءل هل لديك الوقت في جدولك؟
Yes, yes, I do.
نعم، نعم، أفعل.
Of course I do.
بالطبع أفعل.
It just so happens I'm filming in Yuncheng.
لقد حدث أنني أقوم بالتصوير في يونتشنغ.
Let's set up a time to meet later.
دعونا نحدد موعدًا للقاء لاحقًا.
We can discuss the script.
يمكننا مناقشة السيناريو.
Great, thank you, Director.
رائع، شكرا لك يا مدير.
Thank you, Director.
شكرا لك يا مدير.
Zhang Yimu is an internationally renowned director.
تشانغ ييمو هو مخرج مشهور دوليًا.
All the leading actresses he's promoted have become international award winners.
جميع الممثلات الرائدات اللاتي قام بترويجهن أصبحن حائزات على جوائز دولية.
That's wonderful!
هذا رائع!
I finally don't have to worry about the company's attitude anymore.
أخيرًا لم أعد بحاجة إلى القلق بشأن موقف الشركة بعد الآن.
Of course.
بالطبع.
Not just the company,
ليس فقط الشركة،
Don't forget,
لا تنسى،
you're now Chu Jiangchao's woman.
أنت الآن امرأة Chu Jiangchao.
You can walk anywhere in the entertainment industry with confidence.
يمكنك المشي في أي مكان في صناعة الترفيه بثقة.
How does that feel?
كيف تشعر بذلك؟
Feeling more confident now?
هل تشعر بمزيد من الثقة الآن؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
I promise at tomorrow's press conference,
أعدكم في المؤتمر الصحفي غدًا،
I'll definitely give Su Qingyan and Gao Xing
سأعطي بالتأكيد سو تشينغيان وغاو شينغ
a big surprise.
مفاجأة كبيرة.
Then let's have a great collaboration.
إذن فلنحظى بتعاون رائع.
Looking forward to working together.
نتطلع للعمل معًا.
How's the scene?
كيف المشهد؟
Is everything ready?
هل كل شيء جاهز؟
Don't worry, Mr. Su.
لا تقلق يا سيد سو.
Almost all the news media in Yuncheng are here.
تتواجد هنا تقريبا كل وسائل الإعلام الإخبارية في يونتشنغ.
Miss Xiao is backstage.
السيدة شياو خلف الكواليس.
She'll make the announcement herself soon.
وسوف تعلن ذلك بنفسها قريبا.
She'll officially sign with our Qingmu.
ستوقع رسميًا مع فريقنا تشينجمو.
Alright, keep a close eye on things.
حسنًا، راقب الأمور عن كثب.
Make sure there are absolutely no mistakes.
تأكد من عدم وجود أي أخطاء على الإطلاق.
Yes.
نعم.
That's great.
هذا عظيم.
As long as Xiao Yaqi announces the signing,
طالما أعلن شياو يا تشي عن التوقيع،
our product can be launched smoothly.
يمكن إطلاق منتجنا بسلاسة.
It'll be a big hit.
ستكون ضربة كبيرة.
I'm still a little worried.
لا أزال قلقة بعض الشيء.
Don't overthink it.
لا تفكر كثيرا في الأمر.
The only trouble now is Xiao Yaqi.
المشكلة الوحيدة الآن هي شياو ياتشي.
Her contract is still in Miracle's hands.
عقدها لا يزال في يد ميراكل.
As long as she doesn't dare offend her agency,
طالما أنها لا تجرؤ على الإساءة إلى وكالتها،
and doesn't want to be blacklisted,
ولا يريد أن يكون مدرجًا في القائمة السوداء،
she'll definitely have to do as we say.
سوف يتوجب عليها بالتأكيد أن تفعل كما نقول.
Next, let's welcome the popular star Xiao Yaqi.
الآن، دعونا نرحب بالنجم الشهير شياو يا تشي.
Miss Xiao, please come to the stage.
آنسة شياو، من فضلك تعالي إلى المسرح.
It's really her!
إنها حقا هي!
She looks amazing.
إنها تبدو مذهلة.
Wow, Xiao Yaqi is so beautiful.
واو، شياو ياتشي جميلة جدًا.
Yeah.
نعم.
Take pictures, quick!
التقط الصور بسرعة!
Hurry up!
اسرع!
Wow, she's stunning.
واو، إنها مذهلة.
Yeah.
نعم.
Hurry, take a picture!
اسرع، التقط صورة!
So beautiful, so lovely.
جميلة جداً، رائعة جداً.
Here she comes, she's about to make an announcement.
ها هي قادمة، وهي على وشك الإدلاء بإعلان.
Hello everyone, I'm Xiao Yaqi.
مرحباً بالجميع، أنا شياو ياتشي.
I have an announcement.
لدي اعلان.
Because the new product from Qingmu Group
لأن المنتج الجديد من مجموعة Qingmu
has serious quality issues,
لديه مشاكل خطيرة في الجودة،
effective immediately,
ساري المفعول على الفور،
I, Xiao Yaqi, am officially terminating my contract with Qingmu Group
أنا، شياو يا تشي، أنهي رسميًا عقدي مع مجموعة تشينغمو
and will no longer serve as their spokesperson.
ولن يعمل بعد الآن كمتحدث باسمهم.